http://www.danielle-ltd.co.uk/security-and-privacy.aspx

Home / Security and Privacy Policy
Security and Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy applies between you, the User of this Website and Danielle Exclusive Creations Limited (Danielle Creations), the owner and provider of this Website. Danielle Creations takes the privacy of your information very seriously. This privacy policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us or provided by you in relation to your use of this Website. Please read this privacy policy carefully.Definitions and InterpretationIn this privacy policy, the following definitions are used:Danielle Exclusive Creations Limited (Danielle Creations), we or us - , a company incorporated in England and Wales with registered number 02251430 whose registered office is at B1 Hubert Road, Brentwood, Essex, CM14 4JY;Data - collectively all information that you submit to Danielle Creations via the Website. This definition incorporates, where applicable, the definitions provided in the Data Protection Act 1998;Cookies - a small text file placed on your computer by this Website when you visit certain parts of the Website and/or when you use certain features of the Website. Details of the cookies used by this Website are set out in the clause below (Cookies);GDPR - the General Data Protection Regulation 2018 (https://ico.org.uk);UK and EU Cookie Law - the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 as amended by the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) (Amendment) Regulations 2011 (https://ico.org.uk);User or you - any third party that accesses the Website and is not either (i) employed by Danielle Creations and acting in the course of their employment or (ii) engaged as a consultant or otherwise providing services to Danielle Creations and accessing the Website in connection with the provision of such services; andWebsite(s) - the website that you are currently using (www.danielle-ltd.co.uk) and any sub-domains of these sites unless expressly excluded by their own terms and conditions.In this privacy policy, unless the context requires a different interpretation:the singular includes the plural and vice versa;references to sub-clauses, clauses, schedules or appendices are to sub-clauses, clauses, schedules or appendices of this privacy policy;a reference to a person includes firms, companies, government entities, trusts and partnerships;"including" is understood to mean "including without limitation";reference to any statutory provision includes any modification or amendment of it;the headings and sub-headings do not form part of this privacy policy.Scope of this Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy applies only to the actions of Danielle Creations and Users with respect to this Website. It does not extend to any websites that can be accessed from this Website including, but not limited to, any links we may provide to social media websites.Data CollectedWe may collect the following Data, which includes personal Data, from you:NameContact Information such as email addresses and telephone numbersin each case, in accordance with this privacy policy.Our Use of DataFor purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, Danielle Creations is the "data controller".We will retain any enquiry Data you submit for 12 months.Unless we are obliged or permitted by law to do so, and subject to any third party disclosures specifically set out in this policy (see Third Party Websites and Services), your Data will not be disclosed to third parties. This includes our affiliates and / or other companies within our group.All personal Data is stored securely in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998. For more details on security see the clause below (Security).Any or all of the above Data may be required by us from time to time in order to provide you with the best possible service and experience when using our Website. Specifically, Data may be used by us for the following reasons:internal record keepingprocessing enquiriesin each case, in accordance with this privacy policy.Third Party Websites and ServicesDanielle Creations may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with certain processes necessary for the operation of the Website. The providers of such services have access to certain personal Data provided by Users of this Website.Any Data used by such parties is used only to the extent required by them to perform the services that we request. Any use for other purposes is strictly prohibited. Furthermore, any Data that is processed by third parties will be processed within the terms of this privacy policy and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.If you require a full list of suppliers that may have access to your personal data then please contact the GDPR data controller at Danielle Creations by email at brett.bateman@danielle-ltd.co.uk.Links to Other WebsitesThis Website has links to the websitesWe have no control over such websites and are not responsible for the content of these websitesThis privacy policy does not extend to your use of such websitesYou are advised to read the privacy policy or statement of other websites prior to using themChanges of Business Ownership and ControlDanielle Creations may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale and/or the transfer of control of all or part of Danielle Creations. Data provided by Users will, where it is relevant to any part of our business so transferred, be transferred along with that part and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this privacy policy, be permitted to use the Data for the purposes for which it was originally supplied to us.We may also disclose Data to a prospective purchaser of our business or any part of it.In the above instances, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring your privacy is protected.Controlling use of Your DataWherever you are required to submit Data, you will be given options to restrict our use of that Data. This may include the following:use of Data for direct marketing purposes.Functionality of the WebsiteTo use all features and functions available on the Website, you may be required to submit certain Data.You may restrict your internet browser's use of Cookies. For more information see the clause below (Cookies).Accessing your Own DataYou have the right to ask for a copy of any of your personal Data held by Danielle Creations (referred to as a Subject Access Request), where such Data is held, on payment of a small fee, which will not exceed £10.If you would like to make a Subject Access Request then please contact the GDPR data controller at Danielle Creations by email at brett.bateman@danielle-ltd.co.uk.SecurityData security is of great importance to Danielle Creations and to protect your Data we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure Data collected via this Website.If password access is required for certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.We endeavour to do our best to protect your personal Data. However, transmission of information over the internet is not entirely secure and is done at your own risk. We cannot ensure the security of your Data transmitted to the Website.We ensure that any internal systems are password protected and that all reasonable steps have been taken to ensure the physical protection of personal data.CookiesThis Website uses Cookies. Danielle Creations has carefully chosen these Cookies and has taken steps to ensure that your privacy is protected and respected at all times.All Cookies used by this Website are used in accordance with current UK and EU Cookie Law.Before the Website places Cookies on your computer, you will be presented with a message bar requesting your consent to set those Cookies. By giving your consent to the placing of Cookies, you are enabling Danielle Creations to provide a better experience and service to you.You may, if you wish, disable cookie support for this website by using the following links (will open in a new window); however certain features of the Website may not function fully or as intended:Google Chrome - https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416Firefox - https://support.mozilla.org/../enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferencesSafari - https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411Internet Explorer - https://support.microsoft.com/../windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookiesMicrosoft Edge - https://answers.microsoft.com/../how-to-view-and-manage-cookies-in-microsoft-edge/Other Browsers - please consult the help menu in your internet browserThis Website may place the following Cookies:Analytical/performance cookies - They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.Flag cookies - They allow us to recognise if we've notified you about our cookie and privacy policy.You can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your internet browser. By default, most internet browsers accept Cookies but this can be changed.You can choose to delete Cookies at any time; however you may lose any information that enables you to access the Website more quickly and efficiently including, but not limited to, personalisation settings.It is recommended that you ensure that your internet browser is up-to-date and that you consult the help and guidance provided by the developer of your internet browser if you are unsure about adjusting your privacy settings.GeneralYou may not transfer any of your rights under this privacy policy to any other person. We may transfer our rights under this privacy policy where we reasonably believe your rights will not be affected.If any court or competent authority finds that any provision of this privacy policy (or part of any provision) is invalid, illegal or unenforceable, that provision or part-provision will, to the extent required, be deemed to be deleted, and the validity and enforceability of the other provisions of this privacy policy will not be affected.Unless otherwise agreed, no delay, act or omission by a party in exercising any right or remedy will be deemed a waiver of that, or any other, right or remedy.This Agreement will be governed by and interpreted according to the law of England and Wales. All disputes arising under the Agreement will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English and Welsh courts.Changes to this Privacy PolicyDanielle Creations reserves the right to change this privacy policy as we may deem necessary from time to time or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on the Website and you are deemed to have accepted the terms of the privacy policy on your first use of the Website following the alterations.You may contact the GDPR data controller at Danielle Creations by email at brett.bateman@danielle-ltd.co.uk.Last update to this policy: 22 May 2018
Customer Services:
Contact Us
Set Up An Account
Download Catalogue
Pay with:
Track an Order
Returns Policy
Delivery Information
General Information:
Terms and Conditions
Corporate Social Responsibility
Security and Privacy Policy
Site Map
Visit Our Partners:
Danielle Creations Ltd, Studio 08.1.1, The Leathermarket, Weston Street, London, SE1 3ER, England. © Danielle Creations Ltd. 2020 All rights reserved.
×
Be the first to know when this item is back in stock
Enter your email address below and we'll send you an email as soon as this item is back in stock
Email Address:
Tick this box if you would also like to receive any of our newsletters, future promotions or offers via email (opt out at any time)
Privacy Policy
Close
Email Me
